greatis.com 2004-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Greatis Software

**Hot News  
Products  
Downloads  
Ordering  
Projects  
Outsourcing  
Search  
Support  
Contacts  
Partners**

 **** **Newest:**  
RegRun 3  
DesktopKeeper  
Greatis Toys  
Ultimate Pack  
Runtime Fusion  

* * *

| 

**This statement describes the privacy practices we use for our website, transaction of information via E-mail and distribution of our customer list. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free tocontact us. **

**In General**  
In cases where we do keep information about visitors to our site and the E-mail addresses of people who write to us, we store it in our off-line secure computing environment, not on the web. We store this information, but we DON'T sell it or release it to third parties.

**When You Visit Our Site**  
When you visit our site, our computer system records your IP address and the information you enter in on-line forms. There is no personal information about you in these transactions. We can store this information, but we DON'T sell it or release it to third parties.

**When You Send Us E-Mail**  
We read all our E-mail feedback. Our goal is to reply within 72 hours (real average reply time is less than 12 hours) to messages that need a response. Our computer system stores old E-mails and addresses of those who sent them in off-line database, but we DON'T sell or release this information to third parties.

**When You Subscribe to our newsletters**  
We keep your E-mail address on off-line database so we can send you our electronic newsletter. If you cancel your subscription to the newsletter, we delete your address from our database. We DON'T sell or give out E-mail addresses of subscribers to this service. When you order our products your E-mail is added to newsletter receivers database too, but you can cancel this subscription.

**When You Order Our Products**  
All orders processed by SWREG, RegNow and ShareIt payment services. All credit card data are transmitted via their servers, using the secure (encrypted) HTTP protocol according to the current SSL standard. When you purchasing our products, payment service sending us the confirmation message with customer details, but does NOT providing us by any payment information. We are never receiving and not collecting ANY credit card information. Please see privacy statement of [SWREG](http://www.swreg.org/), [RegNow](http://www.regnow.com/) and [ShareIt](http://www.shareit.com/) for more details.

**Our Customer List**  
Our customer list is internally used by our company, [Greatis Software](http://www.greatis.com/). Our customers can modify their personal information and E-mail address by sending E-mail request from the official E-mail address (that was used for purchase) or by sending request from arbitrary address, but with attached registration message that customer received from payment service after purchase. We are sending notification E-mails about all changes of customer's personal informations using official E-mail address. We store and keep all information about our customers private and secure in off-line database and we DON'T sell it or release it to third parties.
